Guide to the The New Leader Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Photographs, 1906-2005, undated
  - Rokossovsky, Gen. Knostantin, undated (Box 187, Folder 85)
  - Romania, 1946-1965 (Box 187, Folder 86)
  - Roman, Salas, undated (Box 187, Folder 87)
  - Romanov, Grigori V., undated (Box 187, Folder 88)
  - Romanov, Mikolai, 1956 (Box 187, Folder 89)
  - Romer, Ray, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 90)
  - Romero, Eduardo Martinez, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 91)
  - Rommel, Erwin, undated (Box 187, Folder 92)
  - Romney, George, 1962-1970 (Box 187, Folder 93)
  - Romulo, Carlos P., undated (Box 187, Folder 94)
  - Roosa, Robert V., 1960 (Box 187, Folder 95)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1949-1960, undated (Box 187, Folder 96)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1938, undated (Box 187, Folder 97)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr., 1952, undated (Box 187, Folder 98)
  - Roosevelt, James, undated (Box 187, Folder 99)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, undated (Box 187, Folder 100)
  - Roper, Elmo, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 101)
  - Rorty, James, undated (Box 187, Folder 102)
  - Rose, Alex, 1957 (Box 187, Folder 103)
  - Rosen, Rabbi David Moses, undated (Box 187, Folder 104)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred, undated (Box 187, Folder 105)
  - Rosenberg, Anna, 1950 (Box 187, Folder 106)
  - Rosenman, Sam, undated (Box 187, Folder 107)
  - Rousset, David, undated (Box 187, Folder 108)
  - Rubin, James P., undated (Box 187, Folder 109)
  - Ruby, Jack, 1963-1964 (Box 187, Folder 110)
  - Rudel, Hans Ulrich, 1976 (Box 187, Folder 111)
  - Rumor, Mariano, 1968-1969 (Box 187, Folder 112)
  - Runley, Edward A., undated (Box 187, Folder 113)
  - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 114)
  - Rusk, Dean, 1960-1968 (Box 187, Folder 115)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1950-1965, undated (Box 187, Folder 116)
  - Russell, Richard B., 1948-1965, undated (Box 187, Folder 117)
  - Russel, Rose, 1950 (Box 187, Folder 118)
  - Russian Revolution, 1917, 1925, undated (Box 187, Folder 119)
  - Rustin, Bayard, 1964-1968 (Box 187, Folder 120)
  - Rwanda, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 121)
  - Ryan, Claude, 1977-1980 (Box 187, Folder 122)
  - Ryan, Joseph P., undated (Box 187, Folder 123)
  - Rykov, Alexei, undated (Box 187, Folder 124)
  - Saar--Scenes, undated (Box 187, Folder 125)
  - Sabry, Aly, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 126)
  - Saburov, Maxim, undated (Box 187, Folder 127)
  - Sacirbey, Muhamed, 1998 (Box 187, Folder 128)
  - Sadat, Anwar, 1970-1977, undated (Box 187, Folder 129)
  - Sadiq, undated (Box 187, Folder 130)
  - Sadlowski, Edward, 1975-1976 (Box 187, Folder 131)
  - Saez, Irene, 1998 (Box 187, Folder 132)
  - Sahara Desert, undated (Box 187, Folder 133)
  - Said, Edward, 1977 (Box 187, Folder 134)
  - Saillant, Louis, undated (Box 187, Folder 135)
  - St. Laurent, Louis, 1949-1952 (Box 187, Folder 136)
  - Saintenny, 1954 (Box 187, Folder 137)
  - St. Kitts, Nevis, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 138)
  - Sakharov, Andrei, 1973 (Box 187, Folder 139)
  - Salam, Saeb, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 140)
  - Salan, Gen. Raoul, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 141)
  - Salazar, Antonio Oliveira, 1946-1962, undated (Box 187, Folder 142)
  - Salinas, 1994 (Box 187, Folder 143)
  - Salinger, Pierre, 1957-1962 (Box 187, Folder 144)
  - Salisbury, Marquees, 1953, undated (Box 187, Folder 145)
  - Salk, Dr. Jonas, 1955, undated (Box 187, Folder 146)
  - Salonga, Jouita, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 147)
  - SALT Talks, undated (Box 187, Folder 148)
  - Saltonstall, Leverett, undated (Box 187, Folder 149)
  - Sampson, Edith, 1950 (Box 187, Folder 150)
  - Samuels, Howard, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 151)
  - Samuelson, Paul, 1970 (Box 187, Folder 152)
  - Sanchez Vilella, Roberto, 1964, undated (Box 187, Folder 153)
  - Sanguinetti, Julio Maria, undated (Box 187, Folder 154)
  - Sandys, Duncan, 1954-1960 (Box 187, Folder 155)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1972-1974 (Box 187, Folder 156)
  - San Marino, undated (Box 187, Folder 157)
  - Santayana, George, 1945-1947 (Box 187, Folder 158)
  - Saragat, Giuseppte, 1947-1963 (Box 187, Folder 159)
  - Sarasin, Pote, 1961 (Box 187, Folder 160)
  - Sarney, Jose, 1985, undated (Box 187, Folder 161)
  - Sarper, Selim, 1961 (Box 187, Folder 162)
  - Sary, Ieng, 1979 (Box 187, Folder 163)
  - Sato, Eisaku, 1964-1971 (Box 187, Folder 164)
  - Saud, King, 1947-1957, undated (Box 187, Folder 165)
  - Saud, Prince, 1999 (Box 187, Folder 166)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1946-1979 (Box 187, Folder 167)
  - Savary, Alain, 1956 (Box 187, Folder 168)
  - Scales, Julius Irving, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 169)
  - Scalapino, Robert, 1966 (Box 187, Folder 170)
  - Scargill, Arthur, 1984 (Box 187, Folder 171)
  - Scelba, Mario, 1948-1954 (Box 187, Folder 172)
  - Scheel, Walter, 1962-1970 (Box 187, Folder 173)
  - Scheele, Dr. Leonard J., 1955 (Box 187, Folder 174)
  - Scherer, Marcel, undated (Box 187, Folder 175)
  - Scherman, Harry, undated (Box 187, Folder 176)
  - Schirdewan, Karl, 1953 (Box 187, Folder 177)
  - Schitthuis, Bernatina, undated (Box 187, Folder 178)
  - Schlaefer, Bishop Salvador, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 179)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., undated (Box 187, Folder 180)
  - Schlesinger, James R, 1971, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 181)
  - Schlomer, Joseph, undated (Box 187, Folder 182)
  - Schmidt, Carlo and Rousset, 1957, undated (Box 187, Folder 183)
  - Schmidt, Helmut, 1965-1980, undated (Box 187, Folder 184)
  - Schmidt-Wittmack, 1954, undated (Box 187, Folder 185)
  - Schools, 1951-1968, undated (Box 187, Folder 186)
  - Schricker, Henry F., 1952 (Box 187, Folder 187)
  - Schroeder, Gerhard, undated (Box 187, Folder 188)
  - Schütz, Klaus, 1967 (Box 187, Folder 189)
  - Schramme, Jean, 1967 (Box 187, Folder 190)
  - Schultze, Charles L., 1977-1978 (Box 187, Folder 191)
  - Schumacher, Kurt, 1950-1951 (Box 187, Folder 192)
  - Schuman, Robert, 1949-1958, undated (Box 187, Folder 193)
  - Schumann, Maurice, 1962-1970 (Box 187, Folder 194)
  - Schutz, Klaus, 1967-1968 (Box 187, Folder 195)
  - Schwartz, Bernard, 1958, undated (Box 187, Folder 196)
  - Scott, Senator Hugh, 1967-1971 (Box 187, Folder 197)
  - Scott, Senator Kerr, undated (Box 187, Folder 198)
  - Scott, Rev. Michael, undated (Box 187, Folder 199)
  - Scott, William, 1962-1964 (Box 187, Folder 200)
  - Scowcroft, Brent, 1980, 1983 (Box 187, Folder 201)
  - Scranton, William, 1964 (Box 187, Folder 202)
  - Scribner, Harvey, 1970 (Box 187, Folder 203)
  - Seaborg, Glenn, 1968-1969 (Box 187, Folder 204)
  - Seale, Bobby, 1969-1970 (Box 187, Folder 205)
  - SEATO, 1960 (Box 187, Folder 206)
  - Seaton, Louis, 1964 (Box 187, Folder 207)
  - Secchia, undated (Box 187, Folder 208)
  - Segni, Antonio, 1955-1962 (Box 187, Folder 209)
  - Segregation, 1957-1960, undated (Box 187, Folder 210)
  - Seidman, William, 1993 (Box 187, Folder 211)
  - Selassie, Haile, 1954-1959, undated (Box 187, Folder 212)
  - Seligman, Daniel, undated (Box 187, Folder 213)
  - Seltzer, Louis, 1949 (Box 187, Folder 214)
  - Selwyn, Lloyd, 1956-1958 (Box 187, Folder 215)
  - Senghor, Leopold, 1961, 1964 (Box 187, Folder 216)
  - Senegal, 1942-1960 (Box 187, Folder 217)
  - Serge, Victor, undated (Box 187, Folder 218)
  - Serov, Ivan, undated (Box 187, Folder 219)
  - Servan-Schreiber, J.J., 1966, 1968 (Box 187, Folder 220)
  - Service, John Stewart, undated (Box 187, Folder 221)
  - The Seychelles, undated (Box 187, Folder 222)
  - Seydlitz, General, undated (Box 187, Folder 223)
  - Shamir, Yitzchak, 1981, 1983 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Shaaka, Bassam--Mayor of Nablus, 1978-1979 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Shah of Iran, 1974-1978 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Shanghai--Scenes, 1945, undated (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1968-1974 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Shapley, Harlow, undated (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Sharaf, Abdul Hamid, undated (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Sharett, Moshe, undated (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Sharansky, Natan, undated (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Shastri, Prime Minister, 1963-1966 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Shaw, Bruno, undated (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Shelepin, Alexander, 1962, 1967 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Sharon, Ariel, 1973-1983, undated (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Shawa, Rashid, 1956 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - Shelest, Pyotr, undated (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - Shen, Guofang, 1999 (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - Shepilov, Dimitri, 1956, undated (Box 188, Folder 17)
  - Sherman, Forrest, undated (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - Shiga, Yoshio, undated (Box 188, Folder 19)
  - Shigemitsu, Mamoru, 1945, undated (Box 188, Folder 20)
  - Shevchenko, Arkady, undated (Box 188, Folder 21)
  - Shihabi, Samir S., 1991 (Box 188, Folder 22)
  - Shin Hyon-Hwack, 1979 (Box 188, Folder 23)
  - Shinwell, Emanuel, undated (Box 188, Folder 24)
  - Shipley, Joseph T., undated (Box 188, Folder 25)
  - Shipping, 1959-1965 (Box 188, Folder 26)
  - Shippingport Atomic Project, 1957-1958, undated (Box 188, Folder 27)
  - Shivers, Alan, undated (Box 188, Folder 28)
  - Sholokhov, Mikhail, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 29)
  - Shore, Peter, 1976-1980 (Box 188, Folder 30)
  - Shotwell, James T., undated (Box 188, Folder 31)
  - Shultz, George, 1968-1988 (Box 188, Folder 32)
  - Shvernik, Nikolai M., 1941 (Box 188, Folder 33)
  - Sierra Leone--Leaders, 1961 (Box 188, Folder 34)
  - Sihanouk, Prince Norodom, 1964-1970 (Box 188, Folder 35)
  - Sihanouk, Ranariddh, 1953 (Box 188, Folder 36)
  - Sikkim, 1958, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 37)
  - Silber, John, undated (Box 188, Folder 38)
  - Silver, Rabbi Abba Hillel, undated (Box 188, Folder 39)
  - Silver, James, 1965, undated (Box 188, Folder 40)
  - Simbolon, Lt. Col. Maludin, 1955-1956 (Box 188, Folder 41)
  - Simon, William, 1976 (Box 188, Folder 42)
  - Simonet, Henri, 1973, 1977 (Box 188, Folder 43)
  - Simonov, Konstantin, 1947, undated (Box 188, Folder 44)
  - Sindermann, Horst, undated (Box 188, Folder 45)
  - Singapore, 1959-1960 (Box 188, Folder 46)
  - Singh, Charan, 1978 (Box 188, Folder 47)
  - Singh, V.P., 1987 (Box 188, Folder 48)
  - Singh, Zail, 1971 (Box 188, Folder 49)
  - Sinyausky, Andrei, undated (Box 188, Folder 50)
  - Sirica, John, 1973 (Box 188, Folder 51)
  - Sirik Matik, Sisowath, 1970-1971 (Box 188, Folder 52)
  - Sisco, Joseph, 1970-1971 (Box 188, Folder 53)
  - Sithole, Ndabaningi, 1975 (Box 188, Folder 54)
  - Skalski, Ernest, undated (Box 188, Folder 55)
  - Slisz, Josef, undated (Box 188, Folder 56)
  - Slansky, Rudolf, 1951 (Box 188, Folder 57)
  - Slave Labor Trial--Brussels, undated (Box 188, Folder 58)
  - Slim, Mongi, 1958-1961 (Box 188, Folder 59)
  - Sloane House Y Demonstrations, undated (Box 188, Folder 60)
  - Slums, 1936-1967, undated (Box 188, Folder 61)
  - Smedley, Agnes, undated (Box 188, Folder 62)
  - Smirnov, Andrei A., 1958 (Box 188, Folder 63)
  - Smith, Adam, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 64)
  - Smith, Dennis C., undated (Box 188, Folder 65)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., undated (Box 188, Folder 66)
  - Smith, Howard W., 1960-1961 (Box 188, Folder 67)
  - Smith, Ian, 1965-1985 (Box 188, Folder 68)
  - Smith, James H., Jr., 1958, undated (Box 188, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Lillian, undated (Box 188, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Margaret C., 1950, undated (Box 188, Folder 71)
  - Smith, Elizabeth, 1960 (Box 188, Folder 72)
  - Smith, Walter Bedell, undated (Box 188, Folder 73)
  - Smylie, Robert E., 1965 (Box 188, Folder 74)
  - Snelling, Richard, 1977-1979 (Box 188, Folder 75)
  - Snow, Sir Charles, 1960, 1964, undated (Box 188, Folder 76)
  - Snyder, Maj. Gen., Howard, 1956 (Box 188, Folder 77)
  - Snyder, John, 1943, undated (Box 188, Folder 78)
  - Soalt, Jerry, undated (Box 188, Folder 79)
  - Soames, Christopher, 1958 (Box 188, Folder 80)
  - Soares, Mario, 1975, 1977, undated (Box 188, Folder 81)
  - Sobell, Marton, 1976 (Box 188, Folder 82)
  - Socarras, Prio, 1948-1949 (Box 188, Folder 83)
  - Socony Vacuum, undated (Box 188, Folder 84)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Natalia, undated (Box 188, Folder 85)
  - Somaliland, undated (Box 188, Folder 86)
  - Somoza, 1955-1978, undated (Box 188, Folder 87)
  - Son Sann, 1980-1981, undated (Box 188, Folder 88)
  - Sonada, Sunao, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 89)
  - Songgram, Pibul Luang, 1951, 1955 (Box 188, Folder 90)
  - Sonnenfeldt, Helmuth, 1970, 1975 (Box 188, Folder 91)
  - Soustelle, 1952-1956 (Box 188, Folder 92)
  - South Africa, 1942-1977, undated (Box 188, Folder 93)
  - Southeast Asia--Mars, 1961-1962 (Box 188, Folder 94)
  - South Molucca, 1978, undated (Box 188, Folder 95)
  - South Pacific Islands, 1937-1967, undated (Box 188, Folder 96)
  - South Vietnam, 1951-1966 (Box 188, Folder 97)
  - Soviet-Chinese Relations, 1969 (Box 188, Folder 98)
  - Soviet Communist Party Congress--22nd--Russia, 1961 (Box 188, Folder 99)
  - Soviet Union
    - Agriculture and Housing, 1941-1977 (Box 188, Folder 100)
    - Celebrations and Demonstrations, 1958-1982, undated (Box 188, Folder 101)
    - Jewry, 1957, 1971, undated (Box 188, Folder 102)
    - Leaders, 1955-1984, undated (Box 188, Folder 103)
    - Leaders in London, 1956, undated (Box 188, Folder 104)
    - Leningrad, 1976 (Box 188, Folder 105)
    - Military, 1946-1980, undated (Box 188, Folder 106)
    - Moscow, 1954-1977 (Kremlin, Lenin’s Tomb, Red Square) (Box 188, Folder 107)
    - Moscow Subway, 1943-1964 (Box 188, Folder 108)
    - Moscow University, 1953-1976 (Box 188, Folder 109)
    - Non-Russian Republics, 1948-1961, undated (Box 188, Folder 110)
    - Paintings, undated (Box 188, Folder 111)
    - People, 1941-1977, undated (Box 188, Folder 112)
    - Shopping, 1947-1980, undated (Box 188, Folder 113)
    - Sights and Scenes, 1953-1980, undated (Box 188, Folder 114)
    - U.S. Exhibition, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 115)
    - U.S. Visitors, 1955-1959 (Box 188, Folder 116)
    - Visitors in U.S., 1955-1961 (Box 188, Folder 117)
    - Wartime Aid, 1942-1945 (Box 188, Folder 118)
  - Spaak, Paul Henri, 1951-1960 (Box 188, Folder 119)
  - Spaatz, Carl A., 1946 (Box 188, Folder 120)
  - Spadolini, Giovanni, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 121)
  - Spain--Civil War, 1931-1939 (Box 188, Folder 122)
  - Spanel, A.N., undated (Box 188, Folder 123)
  - Spain, 1931-1978, undated (Box 188, Folder 124)
  - Sparkman, Sen. John, 1946, undated (Box 188, Folder 125)
  - Speer, Albert, undated (Box 188, Folder 126)
  - Speidel, Gen. Hans, undated (Box 188, Folder 127)
  - Spellman, Cardinal Francis, undated (Box 188, Folder 128)
  - Sperber, Mannes, undated (Box 188, Folder 129)
  - Spiers, Ronald I., 1990 (Box 188, Folder 130)
  - Spiridonov, Ivan, 1962 (Box 188, Folder 131)
  - Springer, Axel, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 132)
  - Sputnik, 1957 (Box 188, Folder 133)
  - Spychalski, Gen. Marron, 1949 (Box 188, Folder 134)
  - Sri Lanka, 1942-1960 (Box 188, Folder 135)
  - Stalin, 1936, undated (Box 188, Folder 136)
  - Stalingrad Battle, undated (Box 188, Folder 137)
  - Stans, Maurice, 1969-1971 (Box 188, Folder 138)
  - Stark, Abe, 1953 (Box 188, Folder 139)
  - Stassen, Harold, 1948-1979, undated (Box 188, Folder 140)
  - Steelman, John R., undated (Box 188, Folder 141)
  - Steel MFG, 1949-1973, undated (Box 188, Folder 142)
  - Steel negotiations, 1959 strike, 1959 (Box 188, Folder 143)
  - Stein, Herbert, 1971-1980 (Box 188, Folder 144)
  - Steinem, Gloria, 1983 (Box 188, Folder 145)
  - Steingut, Stanley, 1964-1965 (Box 188, Folder 146)
  - Stellato, Carl, undated (Box 188, Folder 147)
  - Stenvig, Charles, 1969 (Box 188, Folder 148)
  - Stevens, Robert T., undated (Box 188, Folder 149)
  - Stevens, Siaka, 1967 (Box 188, Folder 150)
  - Stevens, Sinclair M., 1985 (Box 188, Folder 151)
  - Stevenson--Including 1956 Primaries and Conventions, 1956-1961, undated (Box 188, Folder 152)
  - Stevenson--Campaign of 1952, 1952, undated (Box 188, Folder 153)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1952-2003, undated (Box 188, Folder 154)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., III, 1964-1970 (Box 188, Folder 155)
  - Stewart, Michael, 1965 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Stikker, Dr. Dirk, undated (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred, undated (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Stockman, David, 1981-1982 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Stone, Sen. Dick, 1976, 1983, undated (Florida) (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Stone, I.F., 1966-1971 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Stoph, Willi, 1965-1968, undated (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Strachey, John, 1950, undated (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Stratton, William, 1952, undated (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Strauss, Franz Josef, 1956-1980 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Strauss, Lewis L., undated (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Strauss, Robert, 1972-1979 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, undated (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Strijdom, undated (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - Strikes, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 15)
  - Stroessner, Alfred, 1958-1959 (Box 189, Folder 16)
  - Strong, Anna Louise, 1949 (Box 189, Folder 17)
  - Stroudsburg Flood, 1955 (Box 189, Folder 18)
  - Strougal, Lubomir, 1970 (Box 189, Folder 19)
  - Stulberg, Louis, 1966 (Box 189, Folder 20)
  - Suarez, Adolfo, 1976-1977 (Box 189, Folder 21)
  - Subandrio, Dr., 1954-1966 (Box 189, Folder 22)
  - Sudan, 1951-1955 (Box 189, Folder 23)
  - Suez Canal, 1956-1970 (Box 189, Folder 24)
  - Suez Canal--War, 1956, 1969, undated (Box 189, Folder 25)
  - Sugar Workers, undated (Box 189, Folder 26)
  - Suharto, Maj. Gen., 1965 (Box 189, Folder 27)
  - Sukarno, Achmed, 1956-1960, undated (Box 189, Folder 28)
  - Summerfield, Arthur E., 1957, undated (Box 189, Folder 29)
  - Sun Li-Jen, 1950, 1953, undated (Box 189, Folder 30)
  - Supermarkets, 1948-1953 (Box 189, Folder 31)
  - Supreme Court, 1944-1962, undated (Box 189, Folder 32)
  - Suslov, Mikhail, 1959-1966 (Box 189, Folder 33)
  - Suzuki, Mosaburo, 1955 (Box 189, Folder 34)
  - Suzuki, Zenko, 1981 (Box 189, Folder 35)
  - Svoboda, Ludvik, 1945-1968 (Box 189, Folder 36)
  - Swank, Emory, 1970 (Box 189, Folder 37)
  - Sweden, 1935-1973, undated (Box 189, Folder 38)
  - Swee, Dr. Goh Keng, undated (Box 189, Folder 39)
  - Switzerland, 1954-1968 (Box 189, Folder 40)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1957 (Box 189, Folder 41)
  - Symington, Stuart, 1948-1962, undated (Box 189, Folder 42)
  - Syria, 1941-1974 (Box 189, Folder 43)
  - Szczepanski, Jan Jozef, undated (Box 189, Folder 44)
  - Tabuchi, Yoshihisa, undated (Box 189, Folder 45)
  - Tadic, Dusan, 1996-1997 (Box 189, Folder 46)
  - Taft, Robert A., 1950-1952 (Box 189, Folder 47)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1953 (Box 189, Folder 48)
  - Tagore, Rabindranath, 1928-1931 (Box 189, Folder 49)
  - Taiwan, 1957-1990, undated (and Quemoy) (Box 189, Folder 50)
  - Takagaki, Tasuku, undated (Box 189, Folder 51)
  - Takemura, Masoyoshi, 1995 (Box 189, Folder 52)
  - Takenaka, Heizo, 2001-2002 (Box 189, Folder 53)
  - Takeshita, Noboru, 1988-1994 (Box 189, Folder 54)
  - Talabani, Jalal, 1992-2005 (Box 189, Folder 55)
  - Talbott, Strobe, 1993-1999 (Box 189, Folder 56)
  - Talfah, Adnan Khairallah, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 57)
  - Talleyrand, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 58)
  - Talmadge, Herman, 2002, undated (Box 189, Folder 59)
  - Tambo, Oliver, 1986-1993, undated (Box 189, Folder 60)
  - Tambroni, Fernando, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 61)
  - Tamiment, 1956-1961, undated (Box 189, Folder 62)
  - Tamir, Shmuel, undated (Box 189, Folder 63)
  - Tamraz, Roger, undated (Box 189, Folder 64)
  - Tan, Dr. Tony, undated (Box 189, Folder 65)
  - Tanai, Shahnawaz, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 66)
  - Tanaka, Kakuei, 1974-1991, undated (Box 189, Folder 67)
  - Tanaka, Makiko, undated (Box 189, Folder 68)
  - Tanaka, Yasuo, undated (Box 189, Folder 69)
  - Tang, Henry, 2003 (Box 189, Folder 70)
  - Tang, Jiaxuan, 1998 (Box 189, Folder 71)
  - Tanganyika, 1954-1964 (Box 189, Folder 72)
  - Tanks, 1943, 1945, undated (Box 189, Folder 73)
  - Tanner, Vaino, 1939, 1941 (Box 189, Folder 74)
  - Tanzania, undated (Box 189, Folder 75)
  - Tao Siju, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 76)
  - Tapie, Bernard, 1992-1995 (Box 189, Folder 77)
  - Tarloff, Erik, undated (Box 189, Folder 78)
  - Tarwoff, Peter, 1991, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 79)
  - Tate, Stanley, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 80)
  - Taus, Josef, 1975 (Box 189, Folder 81)
  - Tauzin, Billy, 1993-2002 (Box 189, Folder 82)
  - Taxes, 1994, undated (Box 189, Folder 83)
  - Taylor, Charles, 1990-2003 (Box 189, Folder 84)
  - Taylor, George, 1959 (Box 189, Folder 85)
  - Taylor, Morry, 1995 (Box 189, Folder 86)
  - Taylor, Gen. Maxwell D., 1958-1962 (Box 189, Folder 87)
  - Taylor, Sir Hugh, undated (Box 189, Folder 88)
  - Taylor, C.P., undated (Box 189, Folder 89)
  - Taylor, William, 1990-1991 (Box 189, Folder 90)
  - Tebbitt, Norman, 1983 (Box 189, Folder 91)
  - Teeter, Bob, 1991-1992 (Box 189, Folder 92)
  - Teicher, Howard R., 1992 (Box 189, Folder 93)
  - Tekoah, Yosef, 1968, 1970 (Box 189, Folder 94)
  - Tellep, Daniel, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 95)
  - Teller, Edward, 1959-2003 (Box 189, Folder 96)
  - Templer, Sir Gerald, undated (Box 189, Folder 97)
  - Tenet, George John, 1997-2005 (Box 189, Folder 98)
  - Terazawa, Yoshio, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 99)
  - Terekhov, Stanislav, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 100)
  - Mother Teresa, 1989-1997 (Box 189, Folder 101)
  - Ter-Petrosyan, Levon, 1991-1993 (Box 189, Folder 102)
  - Terre Blanche, Eugene, 1985-1992 (Box 189, Folder 103)
  - Terrorists, 1985-1986 (Box 189, Folder 104)
  - Terry, Luther, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 105)
  - Terzi, Zehdi Labib--PLO, 1978-1982 (Box 189, Folder 106)
  - Thach, Nguyen Co, 1989-1990 (Box 189, Folder 107)
  - Thaci, Hashim, 1999 (Box 189, Folder 108)
  - Thackerey, Ted O., undated (Box 189, Folder 109)
  - Thackery, William H., undated (Box 189, Folder 110)
  - Thailand, 1941-1969, undated (Box 189, Folder 111)
  - Thakin Nu, 1949 (Box 189, Folder 112)
  - Thaksin, Shinawatra, 2001, 2003 (Box 189, Folder 113)
  - Thahn, Au Truong, 1966 (Box 189, Folder 114)
  - Thant, U, 1961-1970 (Box 189, Folder 115)
  - Thatcher, Margaret, 1975-2004 (Box 189, Folder 116)
  - Thatcher, Mark, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 117)
  - Thayer, Charles, 1948 (Box 189, Folder 118)
  - Thirring, Hans, undated (Box 189, Folder 119)
  - Thomas, Elbert, 1949, undated (Box 189, Folder 120)
  - Thomas, Elmer, undated (Box 189, Folder 121)
  - Thomas, Norman, undated (Box 189, Folder 122)
  - Thompson, Frank, 1975 (D-N.J.) (Box 189, Folder 123)
  - Thompson, Frank, Jr., undated (Box 189, Folder 124)
  - Thompson, Llewellyn E., Jr., 1955-1958 (Box 189, Folder 125)
  - Thompson, Tommy, undated (Box 189, Folder 126)
  - Thorez, Maurice, 1946-1960, undated (Box 189, Folder 127)
  - Thorn, Gaston, 1975, undated (Box 189, Folder 128)
  - Thorneycroft, Peter, 1962 (Box 189, Folder 129)
  - Thurmond, J. Strom, 1957, undated (Box 189, Folder 130)
  - Thurow, Lester C., 1980-1994 (Box 189, Folder 131)
  - Thuy, Xuan, 1968 (Box 189, Folder 132)
  - Tibet--Scenes, 1933-1957, undated (Box 189, Folder 133)
  - Tikhonov, Nikolai, undated (Box 189, Folder 134)
  - Tijerina, Reyes Lopez, 1967, 1969 (Box 189, Folder 135)
  - Till, Emmett, undated (Box 189, Folder 136)
  - Timerman, Jacobo, 1980, undated (Box 189, Folder 137)
  - Timmerman, George Bell, 1956 (Box 189, Folder 138)
  - Tindemans, Leo, 1974, 1977 (Box 189, Folder 139)
  - Tito, 1950-1971, undated (Box 189, Folder 140)
  - Tixier, Vignancoux, Jean-Louis, 1962, 1967 (Box 189, Folder 141)
  - Toaff, Elio, 1976 (Box 189, Folder 142)
  - Tobacco, 1927 (Box 189, Folder 143)
  - Tobey, Charles, undated (Box 189, Folder 144)
  - Tobin, Austin J., 1959-1960 (Box 189, Folder 145)
  - Tobin, Dan, undated (Box 189, Folder 146)
  - Tobin, Maurice, undated (Box 189, Folder 147)
  - Togliatti, Palmiro, 1947-1963 (Box 189, Folder 148)
  - Togo--Leaders, 1960 (Box 189, Folder 149)
  - Togoland, undated (Box 189, Folder 150)
  - Tojo, Hideki, undated (Box 189, Folder 151)
  - Tokuda, Kyuichi, 1948, undated (Box 189, Folder 152)
  - Toledano, Vincente, undated (Box 189, Folder 153)
  - Tomic, Radomiro, 1969 (Box 189, Folder 154)
  - Toure, Sekou, 1961-1982, undated (Box 189, Folder 155)
  - Tower, John G., 1975, 1980 (Box 189, Folder 156)
  - Toynbee, undated (Box 189, Folder 157)
  - Traffic jams, 1954-1963 (Box 189, Folder 158)
  - Train, Russell, 1973-1975 (Box 189, Folder 159)
  - Trammell, Niles, undated (Box 189, Folder 160)